Aristides Nisotakis

Web Developer

\$\ +30-6957160256 @ niswtis@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Dedicated web developer with expertise in Typescript, CSS, and HTML. Committed to using my knowledge of web technologies to build websites that are both

aesthetically pleasing and easy to use. Persistently working to gain new talents and improve existing ones through practice.

In the interest of contributing to your business and becoming a part of a motivated team with high standards.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

04/2021 - 09/2022

Pluxbox

Hilversum, NL

- Co-supervised a four member team with the goal of creating websites for radio stations all over Europe.
- Developed multiple challenging Front-End DOM structures, such as an Electronic Program Guide and a Radio Rundown.
- Connected intricate systems with the logic of the expanding platform using Typescript, Node is and APIs.
- Assisted in the development of the company's website, in the pursuance of engaging with more clients, by creating a client intake form and implementing cookies.

Intern Web Developer

10/2020 - 04/2021

Pluxbox

Hilversum, NL

- Gained traction with core web development technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, Typescript.
- Utilized the Scrum and Kanban Agile Frameworks to follow the project management process.
- Aligned with the code management flow using Git.
- Strengthened analytical skills in anticipation of the preset deadlines.

EDUCATION

Computer Science

09/2015 - 09/2021

University of Crete

CERTIFICATES

Modern React with Redux [2023 Update]

Development

Node with React: Full Stack Web

Udemy

Udemy

LANGUAGES

English Proficient •••• G

Greek

Native



STRENGTHS

Cooperation & Communication

2 years working with a professional team as well as 4 years of team projects in university.

Logical Thinking

Solutions with a structured mentality for both large and minor issues.

🗼 Decision making

Assisted in the coordination of a professional team, set priorities, and distributed tasks.

Versatility

Interested in learning new things and apply knowledge towards the completeness of tasks.

SKILLS

React.js · Redux · HTML · Typescript ·

CSS · Node.js · MongoDB · Git ·

Javascript

FIND ME ONLINE

in LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aristid es-nisotakis/

Personal Website

https://niswtis.github.io/personalWebsite/

GitHub

https://github.com/niswtis